Misaki-san! All done for the day?
Yeah, I'm checking out.
What?
Daigo, you're still here?
Yeah, Fudo is working the late shift.
I decided to make him some rations.
Truly impressive as ever!
All that on top of scouting
out new heroes for the team.
You must be very busy!
It's not a problem.
Well, Daigo?
Feel like scouting me
as a companion for life?
Indifference...
Indifference
At least don't ignore me!
You're making me cry!
Workplace relationships are off-limits.
As if I don't know that! You goody-goody!
Daigo-san is completely unflappable.
He's calm by nature,
and levelheaded in combat.
He never loses his cool... unlike me.
Yeah. Psychologically speaking,
Daigo is our organization's rock.
I brought dinner.
Thank you, Daigo-san.
Working hard?
I'm writing an exchange diary!
Oh. With the girl who
visited you at the beach?
That's right. I never introduced
the two of you, did I?
Her name is Desumi-san—
Crash
Daigo-san?
D-Desu... Desu...
Desu...mi...
A-Are you all right?!
Desumi... Magahara...
Daigo-san?
Daigo-san?!
Infirmary
Episode 7    Desumi Magahara Is the Monster I Made
Here, some water.
It's appreciated.
Daigo-san...
It's hard to believe, but do
you already know Desumi-san?
Yes.
That's right, you were also born in Hakata.
Do you have some kind of history with her?
Desumi Magahara is the monster I made.
Are you saying you knew her as a child?!
Tell me everything!
Intense
Everything about Desumi-san
that I don't already know!
It's a truly terrifying story.
I'd prefer you not ask unless
you're prepared for the worst.
That's ridiculous!
I'm prepared for anything!
Very well.
I'll tell you, then...
Of the day that the
"Land of Demons," Fukuoka,
became the home of a true demon.
Oda-Style
Karate
This was ten years ago.
Oda-Style Karate
I was still in middle school then.
I was a promising talent
at a famous karate school.
I had no rivals among the older
students, let alone among my peers.
I believed myself the best in the prefecture.
And then... she arrived.
This is Desumi Magahara. She's seven.
Give her your best, everyone.
Oh so cute
Oh so cute...
I'll ask you not to smile
and stare absently, please.
There's far more to the story.
These were the first words out of her mouth:
I try to play with stuff an' always break it.
I'm gonna try hard not to break nothin' here!
Well, look at that little terror!
Daigo, look after her, would you?
Young Desu, was it?
I'd like to see what you can do.
Give me a hit, right here.
A hit?
What's that? Like a punch?
Yes, that's right.
Like this?
Upsy-daisy!
Dai-chan chose the chopsticks!
You're going to start learning karate today.
Gasp!!
D-Did my life just flash before my eyes?
knock
I, the strongest in the dojo,
was nearly killed by a second-grader?!
knock
Sorry. It didn't hurt too bad, did it?
It was an excellent straight punch,
but it didn't even faze me.
S-So cool!
You're the first thing I couldn't break!
Can I hit you again?!
N-Not... today.
I don't want you hurting your fists.
Let's play again, Daigo-niichan!
Little Desumi-san is everything
I'd expect! A true child prodigy!
I didn't entirely believe it at the time.
I chalked it up to dumb luck.
But then, the next day...
Good morning.
Instructor, why are you taking down the sign?
I'm sorry, but I'm closing the dojo.
I was trying to train a second-grader...
and she actually beat me.
I'm a failure as an instructor.
I'm going to become a hermit.
There's no way...
Daigo-niichan!
Young Desu?
I heard the dojo was goin' away.
This is always what happens.
Every place where I have fun
always goes away...
Don't worry, Young Desu.
I'll train you.
So please, no more tears.
Daigo-niichan!
Fair and Equal
Starting today, I will be your teacher.
I had no way of knowing this at the time,
but that was the moment
I'd opened Pandora's box.
You've improved quite a lot.
But I fear you're a long
way from catching up to me.
I was desperate to save face as her teacher.
You're so strong, Instructor!
But all I did was stoke her enthusiasm.
I worked desperately to make myself stronger
just to keep her from killing me.
So Desumi-san is the reason
why you're so strong!
And as the days passed...
Hey! You Desumi Magahara?
Looks like your average
middle schooler to me.
But takin' her down'll be our ticket to fame!
Rumors spread like wildfire,
and soon, Young Desu was forced
to deal with hooligans constantly.
I gotta make dinner for
my little brothers today.
Mind givin' me a break?
Too bad, girlie!
Your little bros'll have
to go hungry tonight!
And soon, Young Desu became known
as the Reaper of Oyafuko-dori.
What a fun nickname!
I'll tease her about it
in our exchange diary.
Then, during the last
winter of high school,
my parents divorced,
and I had to move to Tokyo.
But I had one last piece
of business to take care of.
Settling things with Young Desu!
It's been forever, Daigo-niichan!
Where ya been?
Listen closely, Young Desu.
This will be our final practice.
Let us both give it all we have.
I've been training hard for so
long in anticipation of this day.
I made this monster. Now I must slay it!
Let's begin!
Two minutes later, I lay upon the
ground like a tattered rag.
We said we wouldn't take
it easy on each other,
but you totally held back on me.
I swear to God, I didn't.
What kind of instructor could
go all-out on his student?
What a fool I am.
Farewell, Young Desu.
Daigo-niichan!
Will I ever see you again?
You will not.
When we meet again, will we practice
together again, like we did today?
Absolutely not.
When we do, I promise to go
all-out for the first time!
She wasn't even going all-out back there?
Terrifying...
I left for Tokyo like a man on the run,
and was scouted to be a hero.
It appears the memories
were so frightening to me,
I unconsciously sealed them away.
It's pathetic, I'm sure.
But I can't believe she's here in Tokyo.
What in the world brought her here?
It's because she's a Gekko executive!
She didn't seem to recognize
me during the barbecue,
but it's only a matter of time
until she figures out who I am.
I wonder. Does she still have the power
that earned her the "Reaper" nickname?
M-Most likely.
I see.
Then I must prepare myself.
Fudo, you are aware that workplace
romance is forbidden here, correct?
Yes.
Listen to me.
Tremble
You need to break up with her at once.
What?
I am going to find Desumi Magahara—
D-Daigo-san?
—and s-scout her for our team!
What?!
You're having trouble even saying it.
Of course I'm having trouble.
Th-The thought of even
talking to Young Desu—
The thought of even talking
to her terrifies me!
But this is all for the sake of world peace!
Desperation
As the person in charge of personnel
scouting for a hero organization,
I cannot simply neglect to pursue her talent!
Desumi-san... part of Gelato 5?
I'm Black Gelato! Nice to work with you!
Black Gelato!
Oh so cute
Oh so cute!
Fudo!
First, I need to learn more about her.
Come with me.
I think...
this might end up being
more trouble than expected.
Love After World Domination!
Gusco
N-Now, Daigo-san.
Allow me to officially introduce...
Desumi-san.
It's been so long, Daigo-niichan!
How ya been?
Fine.
You appear to be well, as well.
Tremble
Allow me to explain!
Desumi-phobic Green Gelato,
A.K.A. Daigo Todoroki,
has decided to risk life and
limb to scout Desumi as a hero!
That sure was some surprise!
I never thought you'd turn out
to be a member of Gelato 5!
I didn't recognize you at
the barbecue at all, either!
It's gotta be 'cause you
changed your last name, huh?
Boy, that takes me back!
I can't forget those days
we spent trainin' together.
Daigo-niichan!
I-Indeed.
I know!
You oughta train me again,
just like old times!
I think I've maybe even grown a
little bit stronger since then!
A-Actually...
Come on now, Desumi-san.
Daigo-san is a busy man.
You mustn't make demands on his time.
Fudo...
Relief
That's true.
Disappointment...
I was just so surprised to see you again...
I'm sorry for getting carried way.
Do you think you could do it after all?
Fudo!
That's it!
I'll get something from the drink bar!
Are you all right, Daigo-san?
Trauma isn't something you
can shrug off so easily.
Are you really dating?
She isn't coercing you, is she?
She's not threatening to kill you
if you don't go out with her?
You're making me angry, Daigo-san.
You can trust in one thing:
I truly, truly love Desumi-san.
Y-You're making me blush, Fudo.
Y-You heard that, Desumi-san?
Th-That green tea cake looks delicious.
Would you like a bite?
Aah...
Twitch
H-Hang on a minute!
It's too soon for us to do such things!
That would be an indirect kiss, remember?!
You're so bashful, Desumi-san!
Perhaps it's time to get down to business.
Oh, right...
You were wantin' somethin'
from me, right, Daigo-niichan?
Desumi Magahara...
I've come here to scout you for Gelato 5.
The power you possess
should be used for justice.
Me? A member of Gelato 5?
Daigo-san. About that...
If I was...
Could we be together all the time, then?
Hee hee hee...
Scoop!!
Red & Black
Announce Their Relationship!!
And not only that!
We could date in public,
without fear of scandal!
What do you say, Young Desu?
I'm sorry, Daigo-niichan.
I would love to accept your offer,
but I just can't.
Why not?
What objections could you have?
Gelato 5
New Employee Guide
You Could Be the Sixth!
We offer paid vacation.
I'm more than happy where I am.
I think bein' any happier would
earn me some karmic retribution.
Besides, I've got my hands full with Gekko—
With get-going to school every day, she said!
Right, Desumi-san?
That's right!
I can't say that, not even to Daigo-niichan!
I'm sorry, Fudo.
I was careless.
Yes. We should both be careful.
B-But...
Her lips are so soft!
Blush
Gelato 5 New Employee Guide
You Could Be the Sixth!
Generous Benefits
bap bap
What in the world am I
being forced to look at?
Is this truly Desumi Magahara, the girl
once feared as the Reaper of Oyafuko-dori?
Back when I knew you,
you always seemed lonely, and somehow bored.
You had the air of a woman
isolated by her supremacy.
Say, "Aah"!
Quite frankly...
I sense none of that air of invincibility
you projected back in the day.
Aah...
Love has made you weak!
Desumi
And in that time, I have continued
training via my battles against evil.
That's right, Daigo Todoroki!
What need is there to fear her now?
You can win!
Now is the time to defeat Young Desu,
and conquer your trauma!
Daigo-san?
Step out with me, Young Desu.
I shall fight you, as you wished.
Daigo-san...
Why do you have to fight Desumi-san?
Silence, Fudo.
Are you ready, Young Desu?
If you defeat me in this match, I'll give
up on scouting you for our team.
That's not fair!
There's no way I could possibly defeat you!
And... If I win...
You will give up on your
relationship with Fudo,
and join Gelato 5.
Give up on my relationship with Fudo?
Yes.
Because workplace relationships
are forbidden.
Shoulda told me you had a rule like that.
If that's what you're tellin' me...
This is one battle I can't afford to lose.
Terror
Suddenly and unconsciously,
Daigo Todoroki activated
his suit's transformation!
Five!
The result:
He just barely escaped with his life!
Are you all right, Daigo-san?!
You went easy on me again.
Even after I transformed,
you still think that?
I wanted to stop her,
but I found myself entranced
by her beautiful moves!
And you're always so honest.
What in the world kind of couple is this?
How terrifying...
It's a reunion with my pupil
after so long, after all.
I wanted to give you a win.
And who in the world am I, saying all this?
Never mind.
For now, we'll say it's my defeat.
But, Young Desu...
Promise me one thing.
There are many forces out there that
would seek out power like yours.
If you are to join one of them,
see that it is not Gekko.
It really is a problem.
Does your whole organization
just assume we're a couple?
Yeah... Misaki-neesan is
spreading the rumor everywhere.
They're totally dating!
We have been a little too comfortable lately.
Maybe we need to put some barriers back up.
No more PDA, for one thing.
R-Right.
You're right, Desumi-san.
Grin Grin
What is it?
You're a little upset about that, huh?
I-I'm just being serious!
Don't tease—
Squeeze
Wh-What are you doing?
For instance, if I ever try
to do something like this...
Don't be afraid to push me off, okay?
Oh... Oh so cute!
Oh so cute
Crash
Daigo-san!
N-N-Next...
Next time: "Everybody Has a Secret or Two"!
Episode 8   Everybody Has a Secret or Two
See you then.
Daigo-san!